asus.in 2017-11-04

# Terms of Use Notice / Privacy Policy - Privacy Policy

ASUSTeK COMPUTER INC. and its affiliated companies (hereinafter referred to as “ **ASUS** ”, “ **we/our/us** ”) are committed to protecting and respecting your privacy. We endeavor to comply with all applicable laws on privacy protection and personal information security. ASUS Privacy Policy, together with any additional terms and conditions that contain supplementary information in connection with particular services you are using (hereinafter referred to as “Privacy Policy”), outline our privacy practices regarding the collection, use and safeguard of your personal information through ASUS websites, devices, applications and any services, both online and offline we provide (hereinafter referred to as “SERVICE”), along with whom we may share or disclose the collected information. If you are a minor, you shall access or use the SERVICE only after your parents (or your guardian) read and agree our Privacy Policy. 

The use, access or submission of personal information to the SERVICE by you, or if you are a minor, the submission of your personal information either by your parents (or your guardian) or by you with the permission of your parents (or guardian) to ASUS will be deemed as your acceptance of the Privacy Policy.

### Information ASUS Collect

When you use our SERVICE, we may need to collect certain information from you when use or interact with our SERVICE (hereinafter referred to as “Information”); we may ask for the following information:

#### Information you provide to us

  * Your e-mail address and country/region when you sign up or log in ASUS Member account; if you use your social media account to log in or sign up for ASUS Member account to use our SERVICE, any publicly available information (including but not limited to your profile picture, gender, date of birth and language setting) associated to your social media account may also be collected by us.
  * Your name, mailing/shipping/billing address (including zip code), contact information, e-mail address, credit card number or other payment service information when you make a purchase of our devices, paid services or for certain customer service request.
  * Your name, mailing/shipping address (including zip code), contact information, e-mail, gender, date of birth and ID number when you enter our events or campaigns.
  * Your age, date of birth, gender, height, weight, body temperature, heart rate, blood pressure as well as certain data about your daily activities, for example, your step taken, calories burned and sleep patterns, when you use our healthcare devices or services.

#### Information from your use of SERVICE

  * Device information: such as your device model, serial number, the version and type of your operation system, IP Address, MAC Address, IMEI number and other unique device identifiers.
  * Log information: such as the settings, activation time of your devices, the network you use to connect to our SERVICE, the status of the network, telephony log information, standby status, crash history, preferred interface, type and language settings of browser, diagnose and usage data as well as your usage behavior on our SERVICE.
  * Location information: such as the version of your devices’ GPS and Wi-Fi module, GPS signal, data identifying nearby Wi-Fi access points and cell towers, the time zone and local time where the device is used.
  * Application information: such as the type of your installed applications or software, your usage and interaction with content offered through SERVICE, for instance, the install and uninstall time, frequency of your usage, the category of your preferred applications and software.

### How ASUS use information

We may use information we collect for the purposes below:

  * To assess and improve the SERVICE.
  * To obtain customer feedback and to analyze user experience for the purpose of development and evaluation of new services and devices.
  * To fulfill the sign-up process of ASUS Member account or device registration.
  * To deliver and fulfill any requests made by you, including but not limited to, providing information and documentation regarding purchases such as delivering purchase invoices or proof of purchase; provide software updates and technical notices.
  * To process and fulfill any subscriptions you have signed up for, including ASUS eDMs or newsletters to keep you up to date with the latest ASUS news, promotions and upcoming events. You may unsubscribe it at any time with no charge.
  * To send you important notifications, such as communications about changes to our terms, conditions and policies. Because of the importance of the communications, you may not opt out of receiving these communications.
  * To verify your identity, deliver campaign entries and rewards, provide shuttle services and cover you with insurance if it is a necessity when you enter our events or contests.
  * To assist you on recording, analyzing, modifying and storing information including data about you, your daily activities and the activity results calculated from the data above. Moreover, we will support you on editing and accessing the data and activity results, when you share this information with your family, caregivers, and health care professionals.
  * To provide you with recommendation about services you may be interest in based on your use of our SERVICE.
  * To provide you with marketing communications and advertising that we believe may be of interest of you.
  * To respond to customer support requests, such as product repair requests and respond to your questions.
  * To provide you with our customer care and customer satisfaction survey for user experience analysis.
  * Any other purposes with your consent.

### Retention of information

We will retain your personal information for the period necessary to fulfill the purposes outlined in this Privacy Policy unless a longer retention period is required or permitted by law. We will also by your request to delete your Information collected by ASUS, you may contact us via privacy@asus.com to process such request.

### To whom ASUS disclose your information

Your information will not be disclosed to any third parties without the following exceptions:

#### Your Consent

We will only disclose or share your information to other third parties with your consent.

#### Business Partners

We may disclose hashed and anonymized information to our business partners, for example, business partners who provide data analytics services or advertisings and marketing communications based on the hashed and anonymized information.

#### Service Providers

We may disclose and share your information to our service providers that provide services for or on behalf of us, for instance, service providers assist us with sending marketing communications, providing customer support, delivering purchases and billing. These service providers shall only use your information in compliance with our instruction and with the scope of the purposes hereof; Asus ensures that all of our service providers strictly comply with the Privacy Policy.

#### For legal, protection, security purposes

We may disclose or share your information with third parties for legal or security purposes:

  * To the extent it is required by applicable laws or regulations or competent governmental or judicial authorities, necessary to establish or preserve a legal claim or defense, or necessary to prevent fraud or other illegal activities.
  * To protect the rights, property or safety of ASUS, our service providers, customers or the public, as required or permitted by law.

### International transfers of your information

You understand and consent to the transfer, storage, use or process of your information to ASUS and any of its affiliated companies, service providers who may be located in a different country to you. All said transfer, storage, or process of your information, shall be subject to the Privacy Policy and applicable laws on privacy protection and personal information security.

### Cookies and similar technologies

ASUS uses cookies and similar technologies, such as web beacons to provide our SERVICE:

#### Cookies

Cookies are small text files placed on your devices to personalize your user experience on our SERVICE. Cookies will not collect information that identifies you:  

  * Sign-up and authentication: We use cookies to store your unique sign-up ID number and authentication information on your device. Cookies allow you to visit and move from page to page within our SERVICE without having to log in again on subsequent visits.
  * Storing your preferences and settings: Cookies maintain your settings and preferences on your devices, such as your preferred language or location; by storing the settings in cookies, it is not a necessity to reapply your preferences and settings each time you visit our SERVICE.
  * Analytics: We use cookies to count the number and length of your visit in our SERVICE as well as which part or features you visit the most as well. This information helps us analyze the performance and operation of our SERVICE to improve performance and develop new features, functions and services.
  * Advertising: We use cookies to collect data about your use in our SERVICE and identify your interests, such as the advertisings you have viewed. ASUS, and our business partners, use this data so that we can provide advertising that is most relevant to you.

Please note, you can configure cookies preferences by accessing [tools and settings] of the browser to accept, block or delete cookies. The location of the [tools and settings] of the browser may vary depending on the browser you install, please visit browser’s privacy or support page for further information. Certain features of our SERVICE depend on the use of cookies, if you choose to disable cookies, you may not be able to use the all of the features of our SERVICE.

Cookies used in our SERVICE have been categorized below; you may also refer to the charts to know which cookies we use in our SERVICE and who hosts it:

Category 1: performance Cookies  
Category 2: functionality Cookies  
Category 3: targeting Cookies or advertising Cookies

###### Category 1: performance cookies

Cookies collect information about how you use our SERVICE, for instance which pages you go to most often, and if you get error messages from our SERVICE. Cookies will not collect information that identifies you. All information cookies collect is aggregated and anonymous. They are only used to improve the performance of our SERVICE. Cookie Name | Host  
---|---  
Google Analytics | Google Inc.  
TagMan | Ensighten, Inc.  
eTrack | eTrack Products Pty. Ltd  
Crazyegg | Crazy Egg, Inc  
MIGO | MIGO Corp.  
Yandex Metrica | Yandex Europe AG  
Optimizely | Optimizely, Inc.  
Firebase | Google Inc.  
Hotjar | Hotjar Ltd.  

###### Category 2: functionality cookies

Cookies allow our SERVICE to save your settings and preferences (such as your preferred language or the region you are in) in order to provide you with a more personal and consistent experience each time you visit our SERVICE.

For instance, our SERVICE are able to remember the SERVICE you recently viewed, the number of times you visit the forums listed in our SERVICE or allow you to review the devices you recently compared in our SERVICE. Cookies can also be used to remember changes you have made to text size, fonts and other parts of our SERVICE that you can customize. Cookies may also be used to provide service you have asked for, such as watching a video in our SERVICE. The collected information such as your browsing activities in our SERVICE is anonymized and cannot be tracked by non-ASUS SERVICE.

Cookies Name | Host  
---|---  
Popup | ASUS  
ProductGroup_RelationId | ASUS  
comparecookiename | ASUS  
isBusiness | ASUS  
recently | ASUS  
Lang | ASUS  
Google Tag Manager | Google Inc.  

###### Category 3: targeting cookies or advertising cookies

Cookies are used to deliver advertising that is more relevant to you and your interests by storing how you use our SERVICE. Cookies are also used to limit the number of times you see an advertisement as well as help measure the effectiveness of the advertising campaigns. ASUS places cookies by using advertising campaign services, such as Hubrus DSP, Google AdWords, and Google DoubleClick. The information cookies collect is only used between ASUS and advertising campaign service providers. Cookie Name | Host  
---|---  
Google AdWords: Conversion, and Remarketing Cookies | Google Inc.  
Google DoubleClick | Google Inc.  
Facebook: Conversion, and Remarketing Cookies | Facebook, Inc.  
Adform | Adform  
Hubrus DSP | HUBRUS  

  * Web Beacons  
A web beacon is an often-transparent graphic 1x1 (pixel) GIF or PNG image that is implemented on websites or in an email to measure the effectiveness of campaigns. ASUS or our service providers may use web beacons to know if you visit certain pages or click links in our SERVICE. We may implement web beacons in our marketing communications such as eDMs or ASUS newsletters to know which communication contents you have clicked or read. We will use the information from web beacons to improve our websites and SERVICE.

#### Third-party links in our SERVICE

Our SERVICE may contain links to third-party websites. Please be aware that ASUS is not responsible for the security, the privacy practices and the materials of those third-party websites. We encourage you to be aware of when you leave our SERVICE, and to read the privacy statements of those third-party websites carefully. This Privacy Policy applies to ASUS SERVICE only.

#### Security

We take precautions to protect your information against unauthorized access, alteration, disclosure or destruction. We conduct internal reviews of our information collection, storage and processing practices and security measures, as well as physical security measures to guard against unauthorized access to systems where we store your information.   
Transmission of information between different locations of ASUS and its affiliated companies is performed through our secured wide area network. When you submit your information to us, your information is protected both online and offline.  
However, ASUS cannot guarantee perfect security on the internet. To protect your data from unauthorized access, we recommend that you:

  * To use alphanumerical passwords when signing up ASUS Member account.
  * To change your passwords on a regular basis.
  * To keep your devices up to date by applying the latest available security updates for your software and use such tools as virus/spyware scanners.

If you become aware of a technical vulnerability affecting ASUS SERVICE, please do not hesitate to contact us through  **privacy@asus.com**

#### Manage Your Information

We want to help you keep your information accurate. You may view and change your information by logging in your ASUS Member account and editing your account information. 

If you, or your parents (or guardian) have further inquiries about information ASUS collect about you, such as access, correction, block or deletion your information, kindly contact us through  **privacy@asus.com**

Whenever you use our SERVICE, we strive to maintain the accuracy of your data and protect your information against any accidental or malicious destruction. We will accommodate your requests regarding your data; however, we may not be able to fulfill all your requests in the following circumstances:

  * As required or permitted under application laws;
  * For legitimate business purposes;
  * Unreasonably repetitive requests that require
  * disproportionate technical efforts and resources, for example, developing a new system or fundamentally changing the current practices;
  * Potentially risks on the privacy of others;

#### Minor’s Privacy

We do not knowingly collect information from a minor under the age of thirteen (13), or equivalent minimum age in the relevant jurisdiction, without parental consent. We encourage parents (or guardian) to take an active role in a minor’s online activities and interests while using our SERVICE. 

If you are a minor, please seek parental consent before your use of our SERVICE. You may submit your information with parental consent to us only. Your parents (or guardian) can revoke any consent previously given, request for access, correction, block or deletion of the information at all times.

#### Sensitive Personal Information

ASUS will never ask you to provide sensitive information such as information about your medical or health records, political or religious beliefs, criminal offences (alleged, or committed), criminal conviction background, sexual orientation, sexual history, behavior or genetic information. Please refrain from providing us with such information.

#### Changes to ASUS Privacy Policy

We may change the Privacy Policy from time to time, we highly recommend you periodically review the Privacy Policy posted on our websites. By accessing or using our SERVICE after the Privacy Policy has been updated, ASUS will deem that you consent to the Privacy Policy, including any updates. The most current version of the Privacy Policy will always be available on this page; a prominent notice such as email notification will be delivered to you about any significant changes. You can always check the “updated time” at the bottom for the most current version of Privacy Policy.

#### Contacting Us

If you have any inquiries, questions, comments or complaints about the Privacy Policy, or if you believe that ASUS did not comply with the Privacy Policy, please feel free to contact us. ASUSTeK COMPUTER INC.   
Legal Compliance Department   
Legal Affairs Center   
15, Li-Te Rd.,   
Taipei 112,   
Taiwan  
 **privacy@asus.com**  
Updated June 30, 2017 by ASUS Legal Affairs Center
